{
    "0": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : A.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    27",
            "B.    32",
            "C.    18",
            "D.    23"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "1) There are 567 students in a school. are boys and the rest are girls. There are 9 times as many girls as there are teachers. How many teachers are there?"
    },
    "1": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : C.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    6542",
            "B.    3468",
            "C.    5698",
            "D.    4376"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "2) 3/4 of the books in the library are English books and the rest are Chinese books. There are 2849 more English books than Chinese books. What is the total number of books in the library?"
    },
    "2": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : B.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    1 kg",
            "B.    2 kg",
            "C.    3 kg",
            "D.    4 kg"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "3) A full tin of paint has a mass of 27 kg. When the same tin is 2/5 filled with paint, it has a mass of 12 kg. What is the mass of the empty tin?"
    },
    "3": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : C.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    56",
            "B.    28",
            "C.    32",
            "D.    64"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "4) Twice a number is 48 greater than 1/2 of the number. What is the number?"
    },
    "4": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : A.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    130",
            "B.    140",
            "C.    100",
            "D.    150"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "5) Rani read 52 pages of a book on Monday. On Tuesday, she read 1/6 of the remaining pages. If she still had half of the book left to be read, how many pages were there in the book?"
    },
    "5": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : D.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    128",
            "B.    234",
            "C.    98",
            "D.    224"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "6) Raja sold 1/4 of his eggs on Saturday and 1/6 of the remainder on Sunday. If he had 140 eggs left, how many eggs did he have at first?"
    },
    "6": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : D.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    160",
            "B.    180",
            "C.    200",
            "D.    210"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "7) There are some pens in a box. 1/3 of them are black, 1/2 of them are red and the rest are green. If there are 35 green pens, how many pens are there altogether?"
    },
    "7": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : C.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    380,000",
            "B.    400,000",
            "C.    420,000",
            "D.    440,000"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "8) In a country, 7/10 of the population are Chinese. 2/3 of the remainder are Malays and the rest are Indians. If there are 60,000 Indians, how many Chinese are there?"
    },
    "8": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : C.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    55",
            "B.    65",
            "C.    75",
            "D.    85"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "9) 2/5 of Raja's money can buy 40 books. How many books can he buy with 3/4 of his money?"
    },
    "9": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : D.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    198",
            "B.    212",
            "C.    226",
            "D.    248"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "10) Rani has 372 beads. 1/6 are blue and the rest are red. How many more red beads are there than blue beads?"
    }
}